I'm sure by now many of you know that a group of journalists was just intentionally targeted
with a kinetic strike by the Israeli military in the Al Jazeera journalist tent in Gaza City
because they do their targeting operations based off cell phone signals so somewhere someone in
the targeting cell was like all these journalists are here drop it and it's hard to do a battle
damage assessment based off of this video but it's clearly there's no crater it was not a bomb
it was most likely a precision munition like a hellfire missile shot from a Q9 Reaper drone
as you can see there's no blasted terrain okay so basically I've been tracking this for a long time
when they go to kill journalists or aid workers they use precision munitions like this because
they want to be able to see the bodies see on thermal imaging the heat go away out of the
bodies so they can confirm that they're dead you can't do that if you're trying to kill a high value
target with a bomb because it just destroys everything there's a drone somewhere circling
above making sure all of these guys are dead this strike was not about leveling Gaza this one
was to kill the prominent journalists reporting the genocide so uh rest in power y'all and are there
any quote-unquote Western journalists that would like to say anything about this about your colleagues
who are being as a matter of state policy targeted and assassinated specifically so they don't do their
jobs